export const QuizData = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: `Where can you find the Seven Coloured Earths?`,
    options: [`Fiji`, `Malaysia`, `Mauritius`, `India`],
    answer: `Mauritius`,
  },
  {
    id: 0,
    question: `Which central South American country is home to the largest salt flats in the world?`,
    options: [`Bolivia`, `Peru`, `Argentina`, `Chile`],
    answer: `Bolivia`,
  },
  {
    id: 0,
    question: `Victoria Falls is a waterfall on which Southern African river?`,
    options: [`Limpopo River`, `Congo`, `Nile River`, `Zambezi River`],
    answer: `Zambezi River`,
  },
  {
    id: 0,
    question: `Where is the Blue Lagoon geothermal spa?`,
    options: [`New Zealand`, `Iceland`, `Canada`, `Norway`],
    answer: `Iceland`,
  },
  {
    id: 0,
    question: `Where in the Caribbean can you swim with pigs?`,
    options: [`Puerto Rico`, `Virgin Islands`, `Bahamas`, `Trinidad & Tobago`],
    answer: `Bahamas`,
  },

  {
    id: 0,
    question: `Which is the only developed country without legally mandated vacations?`,
    options: [`United States`, `China`, `Portugal`, `Australia`],
    answer: `United States`,
  },

  {
    id: 0,
    question: `Which is a United States territory?`,
    options: [`Hawaii`, `Northern Mariana Islands`, `Bahamas`, `Fiji`],
    answer: `Northern Mariana Islands`,
  },

  {
    id: 0,
    question: `Which is the smallest country in the world?`,
    options: [`Tunisia`, `Malta`, `Vatican City`, "Delaware"],
    answer: `Vatican City`,
  },

  {
    id: 0,
    question: `Which is the national animal of Scotland`,
    options: [`Badger`, `Hedgehog`, `Wolf`, `Unicorn`],
    answer: `Unicorn`,
  },

  {
    id: 0,
    question: `In which country did coffee originate?`,
    options: [`Colombia`, `Ethiopia`, `Jamaica`, `Sumatra`],
    answer: `Ethiopia`,
  },
];
